FABIO PETRELLA

Full Stack Developer

Personal Portfolio Personal Portfolio Personal Portfolio

SUMMARY

Web Developer with ability to learn and collaborate in rapidly changing environments, a 1-year intensive training in Full Stack Web Development (MERN stack) and many hours of self-taught coding. Seeking for a position to apply the results of my previous experiences combined with acquired skills, to challenge myself and deliver creative solutions.

Highly motivated, critical thinker and team-work oriented.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Developer DCI Digital Career Institue gGmbH

2021 - Ongoing Berlin, DE

- o Accomplishing a one-year-full-time training including technologies from MERN stack
- $_{\circ}\,$ Completing multiple small and one final practical project to practice programming skills

Food Specialist

2014 - 2015 L'Aquila, IT

Niko Romito Formazione e Consulenza SRL

- O Accomplished a nine-month-full-time training, Reale, Michelin 3 Star Restaurant
- Completed final exam with a rating of 52/60

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sous-Chef

03/2019 - 12/2019 Berlin, DE

Lab Kitchen, act.3 GmbH

- $\circ\,$ Responsible for managing and directing the kitchen staff, shifts and job positions
- $\circ\;$ Developed new menu options based on seasonal changes and customer demand
- Ensured that kitchen activities operate in a timely manner

03/2018 - 02/2019 Berlin, DE

Chef de Partie

A Common Ground, Silo Coffee Gmbh

- $\circ\,$ Gave attention productivity of the kitchen such as speed and food quality
- $_{\circ}$ Provided support to junior kitchen employees with various tasks including line cooking
- o Recruited and trained new kitchen employees to meet restaurant and kitchen standards



SKILLS

- Javascript React CSS3 •
- SASS Bootstrap ES6 •
- HTML5 NodeJS •
- MongoDB Express •
- JsonWebToken Git •

PROJECTS

SightSpot

Full Stack App built with React, ExpressJS, Bootstrap

https://sightspot.herokuapp.com/

Rock, Paper, Scissors

Game built with Javascript, CSS, Html

https://fbgameproject.netlify.app/

Shrugman/Bulls and Cows

Command Line Games built with Javascript, Prompt-sync, Node.js

https://github.com/fbphc/Final-Project-DCI-Programming-Basics

CERTIFICATES

Udemy - Javascript Course 2022

LANGUAGES

Italian - Native Speaker

English - Full Professional Proficiency

German - Prof. Working Proficiency

Spanish - Elementary Proficiency

LINKS





Certiflicate no: UC-21b96142-54c5-4c57-b036-bddc4c275c00
Certiflicate url: ude.my/UC-21b96142-54c5-4c57-b036-bddc4c275c00
Reference Number: 0004



CERTIFICATE OF COMPLETION

The Complete JavaScript Course 2022: From Zero to Expert!

Instructors Jonas Schmedtmann

Fabio Petrella

Date July 1, 2022 Length 69 total hours